this is an urgent appeal to people from Russia
это срочное обращение к людям из России
from the Russian Federation who watch
из Российской Федерации которые смотрят
me on my channel or got here by
меня мой канал или попали сюда случайно
chance these days when the
в эти дни когда
armed forces of Ukraine grind
вооруженные силы Украины перемалывают на
this Kharkov Russian group into mincemeat,
фарш вот эту харьковскую группировку
which was an occupation
российскую которая была оккупационная
Vladimir Putin, your king whom you
Владимир Путин ваш царёк которого вы
love adore who you think that he
любите обожаете который думаете что он
honors  he worries about you what he
чтит вас переживает за вас он что он
does he congratulates he does not congratulate he
делает он Поздравляю Не поздравляет он
expressed his condolences to the new king
высказал соболезнования королю новому
there karma the third
там карму третьему
in connection with the death
в связи со смертью
of Queen Elizabeth II
королевы Великобритании Елизаветы 2
With the help of this weapon, these days your Putin is
с помощью этого оружия эти дни валят
bringing down Russian rashists in the
рашистов на
Kharkiv region
харьковщине
. He didn’t even say a word
ваш Путин Он даже слово словно не сказал
about your dead children about your
про погибших ваших ребятишек про ваших
paratroopers there from hoops of mobiks from
там десантников с обручков мобиков из
tandemir.
тандемир всю эту
then for this person, this
Подумайте что для этого человека этого
dwarf who sits in the Kremlin, you are nobody,
карлика который сидит в Кремле вы никто
so the Queen for him is the major
так вот Королева для него это высшая
league with whom he is going, for example, he
лига с которыми он собирается например
wants to see himself at the table of some kind of
хочет видеть себя за столом каких-то
negotiations, he himself is some kind of
переговоров он себя каким-то
historical Personality Well, for him you are
исторической Личностью Ну вы для него
just the meat of the empire, so very  it’s important to
просто мясо империи поэтому очень важно
tell everyone you know so who they
передайте всем всем знакомым так их кого
may be agitating to go to fight in Ukraine
может агитирует ехать воевать в Украину
who may have already decided to go somewhere
кто может уже где-то собрался ехать
Ukraine Tell it, you show
Украина Рассказывайте это показываете
that these people don’t
что эти люди для Путина мяса так не
need to go to Ukraine to fight meat for Putin because
нужно ехать в Украину воевать потому что
your homeland will throw you there and won’t
тебя Родина там твоя кинет кинет и не
remember  he will remember the queen of british
вспомнит о королеву британскую вспомнит
And you will rot somewhere, they
А ты будешь гнить где-то
created you in Ufa, who will recruit whom in the
поцарата вам создали Уфой кто кого
region, you will rot in an unmarked
региона наберут будешь гнить безымянной
grave, they will put crosses there, he
могилки поставят крестики там
will write even with honors, don’t bury,
напишет даже с почестями не Похороните
but Lada Kalina can be
но Ладу Калину может получится родителям
raised by parents, so
поднять поэтому обязательно обязательно
be sure to tell everyone if you are afraid
всем передавайте если там Боитесь
to speak publicly, discard  friends to
публично выступать скидывайте друзьям
some acquaintances who may have
каким-то знакомым которые возможно
thought
думали
about participating in  this so-called military
о участие в этой так называемой военной
operation to cut down the dough will not be
операции чтобы срубить бабла бабла не
cut down because the armed forces of
срубят потому что вооруженные силы
Ukraine are already pumped up with foreign
Украины уже накачаны иностранной
equipment so that they can
техникой настолько что они могут
carry out high-quality offensive
проводить качественные наступательные
operations and we see this, the Russian army
операции и мы это видим Российская армия
turned out to be an inflated zilch, so save the
оказалась дутым пшиком поэтому сохраните
lives of your guys and do not meddle in Ukraine
жизни своих ребят и не лезьте в Украину
also If you  just work somewhere in
также Если вы просто работаете где-то на
state enterprises And even if
государственных предприятиях И даже если
in state in private You can
на государственных на частных Вы можете
help the collapse of the system just do
помогать краху системы просто делайте
your job very, very slowly
свою работу очень-очень медленно
sabotage the Italian strike Like
саботируйте итальянская забастовка Вроде
it's called if you need to do
это называется если вам нужно там делать
some details there do them without a
какие-то детали делать их без
certain
определенного
enthusiasm do them  go slowly
воодушевление делайте их медленно ходите
often for a smoke break drink coffee for some
часто на перекур пейте кофе на какие-то
arrange some unnecessary
устраивайте какие-то ненужные
many hours of meetings The bottom line is
многочасовые совещания Суть в том что
that this system The Empire is so on
вот эта система Империя так на глиняных
clay it must be loosened And the
на она должна расшатываться И чем
faster it loosens, the faster
быстрее она расшатается чем быстрее вот
this entire oligarchic Putin power
эта вся олигархическая Путинская власть
collapses, the faster you  cm  you can
рухнет тем быстрее вы сможете
transform your country on some new basis
преобразовать на новых каких-то началах
Yes, there will be new
свою страну Да возникнут новые
Republics of Bashkortostan Tatarstan in the
Республики Башкортостан Татарстан на
Caucasus there will be independent republics of
Кавказе будет независимые республики
Buryatia, the
Бурятия
peoples will receive their independence from
народы получат свою независимость от
Moscow and even
Москвы и даже
regional ones will be Republics that
региональные будут Республики которые
will leave resources in their own country
будут оставлять ресурсы у себя в стране
to give to Moscow so that Muscovites
отдавать в Москву чтобы москвичи там
fatten there buy yachts  Sechin’s fur coats you
жировали яхты покупали шубы у Сечина вы
were sitting there, that’s why even now for Putin the
там сидели поэтому еще сейчас для Путина
British Queen is more important than the Russian
Британская королева важнее русского
soldier about whom they sing so much,
солдата про которого так воспевают
therefore, because the Russian soldier is
поэтому потому что русский солдат это
nobody else since Peter’s time, this
никто еще со временем Петра iходит эта
bike goes to Take care of the guns and the soldier of the woman
байка чтобы Берегите пушки а солдат бабы
still gives birth, here’s the problem that the
еще нарожает вот проблема что уже и
birth rate has already fallen,
рождаемость упала
therefore
поэтому
remember your enemy is not in Ukraine your enemy
помните ваш враг не в Украине ваш враг
is in the Kremlin
сидит в Кремле
he is
он
his clique robbing you All these years
его клика грабит вас Все эти года
and soon it will end help to
и скоро ему придет конец помогайте
shake this Empire in the middle Glory to Ukraine
шатать эту Империю середины Слава Украи